

# **About me**

Enthusiastic and creative engineering student with 5 years of computer science apprenticeship. A dedicated student who easily adapts to different learning styles. I can describe myself as an ambtious person with critical thinking and decision

# Office:

Word, Excel, PowerPoint.

#### **Software:**

 Adobe Premiere Pro, Adobe Photoshop CS6, Visual Studio Code, Intelij, Eclipse, SQL Server, SharePoint, Soap UI.

# Skills:

- DevOps, CICD Intégration jenkins et sonarqube, Sonar, Ansible, git, Azure, Docker, kubernetes, Monitoring, Design pattern, Testing, Agile, scrum.
- JAVA, JEE, C , CPP, ASP.NET, ORACLE, SQL, Spring, API JPA, Hibernate. Bootstrap, angular, ReactJS MERN, Django, Data science, Ardouino, Android, flutter, Administration Windows/linux.

# **Certification:**

- 1.Introduction to the Java Spring 101 Framework: Simplilearn
- 2. JAVA Fundamentals: SoloLearn
- 3. Devops and Software Engineering Professional Certificate: IBM
- 4. Dot Net Fundamentals: Great Learning
- 5. Containerize Java microservices in Docker: IBM
- 6. Big data Fundamentals: IBM
- 7. AWS Fundamentals: Amazon
- 8.Digital, social, entrepreneurial and personal skills: Honoris Universities

# **Hobbies:**

- Reading and writing: Slam
- Sport: Swimming, basketball
- Cinema and theater:Thriller/Drame
- Leadership & Advisor : Enactus Asian Culture Club

# Languages:

- Arabic : native language.
- French: DELF B2.
- English: Advanced.

# **AYOUB** CHAWKI

Software development engineering student

- **(** +212 6 32 55 66 06
- ayoubchawkipros@gmail.com
- https://github.com/ayoubchawkiPRO
- 124th Street ibn mounir floor 2 apt 9 Maarif, Casablanca,
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/ayoub-chawki-1128a81b5/
- https://ayoubchawkipro.github.io/ayoubchawki.github.io/

Looking for a 6 month end of study internship starting in March 2023

#### **Formation**

#### 2020 - 2023 | Engineering degree

• Student in the 3rd year of the engineering cycle in computer engineering and networks, option computer methods applied to business management at the Moroccan School of Engineering Sciences in Casablanca (Honoris)

#### 2017 - 2020 | Technical University degree

• University Diploma of Technology in Computer Engineering, System and Network Administration option at the Higher School of Technology of Safi (Cady Ayyad University)

#### 2016 - 2017 | High school degree

• Baccalaureate in Physics and Chemistry at Lycée la Sagesse in Safi (mention bien)

# **Professional experiences**



Jul 2022 - Sep 2022 · 3 mos

#### Internship at Expertise Data Casablanca, Morocco.

- Conception and development of a web infrastructure and internal management of the company Expertise Data with JEE and Angular and deployment.
- Administration and development **Ldap** authentication with spring boot security and oracle under windows server 2019.
- Jul 2021 · 1 mo

#### Internship at BC Skills in Safi, Morocco.

• Design and development of an Odoo platform and an Android application for the recruitment management of BC SKILLS with Java.

### Apr 2020 - Jun 2020 · 3 mos

#### Internship at Safi EST Higher School of Technology in Safi.

· Realization of a detection and recognition application using deep learning algorithms with python and matlab.

#### Jul 2019 · 1 mo

#### Internship in the information systems department at OCP in Safi.

• Realization of a hardware reform application with java and MySql with the development team.

#### Jul 2018 - Aug 2018 · 2 mos

### Internship at the radess of Safi, Morocco.

• Realization of a chat application for radess employees with html, css, js, php and MySql.

# **Academic Projects:**

- Spring Data Angular Digital Banking JEE project.
- Medical consultation application with Django machine learning and flutter.
- Car rental application with ASP.NET and SQL server.
- Java CICD with Jenkins and Azure Web Apps.
- Human resource management application MVC with django.
- Chat bot with react node is MERN and Tensorflow.
  - Remote controlled ardouino robot with android app using Java for detecting objects with matlab.